Steps to create and initialize the database: 
- open PhpMyAdmin page (MySQL DBMS) and import news.sql
- A Database named ‘news’ with 3 Tables (‘user’, ‘email’, ‘article’) will be created.
- Update mysql db connection details at database.php under code-igniter config  folder.

Steps to prepare the source code to build/run the application properly:
- Move crossover folder to your php hosting (either online or local).
- Point your domain name or localhost to all the contents inside the folder crossover.
- Visit your domain name or localhost and you will find my application login page.

Assumptions: 
- Assuming you know how to setup a full stack Apache, MySql, and Php on your localhost or on online hosting.
- I assumed that pictures will be hosted on another hosting service and the user will only publish the picture URL in our database. 
- I assumed the it is a simple news publishing system that doesn’t support publishing html-formatted or rich-formatted news text.

Notes:
- I have no prior experience with unit testing. However, I did my best to develop unit tests that can be run by visiting http://localhost/test
- I am using Mac OSX so Wink doesn’t support OSX. However, I created a screen recording using QuickTime Player and compressed it to crossover.m4v
- I created a view for the missing requirement to reset user password. However, backend codes aren’t completed yet. 

Feedback:
- Thank you for sending the pre-condition information before the assignment starts since setting up the environment takes some time. 
- For any help, please email me [Ahmed Moussa] at nagar@aucegypt.edu or ahmsayat@gmail.com
- Thank you. 

